https://www.money-zine.com/about/information/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting Money-Zine.com. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at Money-Zine.com.
The Information We Collect
At Money-Zine.com, you might vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to an online newsletter, or participate in an online community. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages might include: name, address, e-mail address, and information about your interests in and use of various programs, and services.
In certain sections of Money-Zine.com, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to view content targeted to community members.
We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Safari), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows, Linux, or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, Time Warner, Verizon).
How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our services, to respond to inquiries about our offerings, and to offer other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  We may also use the information to fulfill a request by you for our online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.
The information we collect in connection with an online forum or community is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.
Employees of Money-Zine.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.  For example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Money-Zine.com.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosure of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
Finally, Money-Zine.com will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
Money-Zine.com uses only reputable third party agencies to present or serve advertisements.  Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with Money-Zine.com, many of our web pages use "cookies," which are text files placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information.
Money-zine.com uses third-party advertisements to help support the website.  Advertisers (such as Google's AdSense program) may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise. This can send to these advertisers' information including your IP address, ISP, the browser you're using, and in some cases whether you have Flash installed.  This information is generally used for geotargeting purposes.  For example, showing New York insurance advertisements to someone located in New York.  They can also be used to show certain ads based on the pattern of websites you may have visited in the past.
When this website is publishing advertisements from Google, those advertisements may use the DoubleClick DART cookie.  The DART cookie enables Google to serve ads based on user visits to Money-zine.com as well as other websites participating in Google's advertising program.  Users may opt out of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Money-Zine.com uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), or save your password in password-protected areas.
This website also uses Google Analytics Advertiser Features, which provides information about Google Display Network Impressions, integrates with DoubleClick, and allows us to use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.  This feature enables third-party vendors to integrate first-party identifiers such as the Google Analytics cookie, with third party identifiers such as the DoubleClick cookie.  Users of this website have the right to opt-out of these programs.
Commitment to Security
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the Money-Zine.com privacy policy, you may contact us at privacy@money-zine.com.
Welcome | Privacy Statement | FAQs | Contact Us | Advertise | Career Opportunities | Disclaimer | Copyright Notice
